zahra abdoulkarem haron

Makkah, Saudi Arabia



zahra9amdulkarem@gmail.com



+966 594 769 828



linkedin.com/in/zahraabdoulkarem



https://github.com/zahra-abdulkarem

Summary

What is the importance of the website for business owners, whether they are companies or individuals?

The website allows the formation of a better relationship with customers, because it allows you to send instant messages to them via e-mail, and customers can review products online and leave their comments and opinions, and for that it is important to have a website.

I'm a front end web developer, I'm use

- node.js
- React
- Bootstrap5

I started learning this field in 2022 and I have simulated restaurant websites and some small projects, and I am still learning and developing my skills and experiences in the field of front-end development, back-end development, and problem-solving.

You can contact me on my email zahra9amdulkarem@gmail.com

Experience



Frontend Web Developer

Self-employed

Jul 2022 - Present (10 months)

Building, designing and developing website interfaces



Mathematics Teacher

No-Company

Mar 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

I taught mathematics and computer science privately to primary and middle school students, and I trained them to solve complex mathematical issues, logical thinking, and detailed problem-solving.

Education



The-eighth high school

Natural Sciences

Jan 2018 - Aug 2020

Through my studies in the-eighth high school, I learned a lot of skills, the most important of which is the skill of communication and working as a team. The school helped me discover my passion in technology in general and programming in particular.

Skills

HTML • Node.js • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • React.js • تطوير الويب • Github • HTML5 • CSS Grid Layout • SASS